1. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/lst_Source"), Source, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
5. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_BatchAmount"), BatchAmount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
9. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_BatchAmount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
13. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/chk_Split"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
17. check(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/chk_Split"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
21. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/lst_Type"), Type, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
25. clearText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Amount"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
29. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Amount"), Amount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
33. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Amount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
37. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_CheckRef"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
41. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_CheckRef"), CheckRef, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
45. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/lst_PaymentInstrument"), PaymentInstrument, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
49. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_Split"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
53. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_Split"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
57. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
61. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
65. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypePaymentAccount"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
69. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypePaymentAccount"), SplitTypePayment, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
73. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAccount"))
77. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAccount"), SplitAccount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
81. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAccount"), Keys.chord(TAB), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
85. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAccountAmount"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
89. clearText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAccountAmount"))
93. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAccountAmount"), SplitAccountAmount)
97. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAccountAmount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
101. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAccountDescription"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
105. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAccountDescription"), SplitAccountDescription, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
109. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
113. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
117. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypePaymentInvoice"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
121. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypePaymentInvoice"), SplitTypePayment, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
125. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitInvoice"))
129. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitInvoice"), SplitInvoice, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
133. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitInvoice"), Keys.chord(TAB), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
137. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitInvoiceAmount"))
141. clearText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitInvoiceAmount"))
145. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitInvoiceAmount"), SplitInvoiceAmount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
149. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitInvoiceAmount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
153. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitInvoiceDescription"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
157. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitInvoiceDescription"), SplitInvoiceDescription, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
161. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
165. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
169. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypePaymentAgency"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
173. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypePaymentAgency"), SplitTypePayment, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
177. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgency"))
181. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgency"), SplitAgency, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
185. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgency"), Keys.chord(TAB), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
189. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyAmount"))
193. clearText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyAmount"))
197. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyAmount"), SplitAgencyAmount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
201. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyAmount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
205. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyDescription"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
209. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyDescription"), SplitAgencyDescription, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
213. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
217. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
221. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypePaymentAgencyStatement"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
225. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypePaymentAgencyStatement"), SplitTypePayment, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
229. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyCode_ABStatement"))
233. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyCode_ABStatement"), SplitAgency, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
237. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyCode_ABStatement"), Keys.chord(TAB), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
241. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyStatement"))
245. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyStatement"), SplitAgencyStatement, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
249. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyStatement"), Keys.chord(TAB), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
253. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyStatementAmount"))
257. clearText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyStatementAmount"))
261. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyStatementAmount"), SplitAgencyAmount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
265. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyStatementAmount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
269. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyStatementDescription"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
273. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyStatementDescription"), SplitAgencyStatementDescription, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
277. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
281. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
285. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypePaymentAgencyDBComm"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
289. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypePaymentAgencyDBComm"), SplitTypePayment, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
293. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyCode_DBStatement"))
297. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyCode_DBStatement"), SplitAgency, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
301. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyCode_DBStatement"), Keys.chord(TAB), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
305. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/chk_SplitAgencyDBComm"))
309. check(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/chk_SplitAgencyDBComm"))
313. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/chk_SplitAgencyDBComm"), 0, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
317. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyDBCommAmount"))
321. clearText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyDBCommAmount"))
325. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyDBCommAmount"), SplitAgencyDBCommAmount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
329. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyDBCommAmount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
333. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyDBCommDescription"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
337. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitAgencyDBCommDescription"), SplitAgencyDBCommDescription, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
341. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
345. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_AddSplit"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
349. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypeSuspense"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
353. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/lst_SplitTypeSuspense"), SplitTypeSuspense, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
357. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitSuspenseAmount"))
361. clearText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitSuspenseAmount"))
365. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitSuspenseAmount"), SplitSuspenseAmount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
369. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitSuspenseAmount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
373. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitSuspenseDescription"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
377. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/txt_SplitSuspenseDescription"), SplitSuspenseDescription, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
381. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_SplitOK"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
385. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/btn_SplitOK"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
389. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/btn_Next"), 7, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
393. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/btn_Next"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
397. BatchNumber = getText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/val_BatchNumber"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
401. comment("Posted Payment Batch Number " + BatchNumber)
405. CheckRef = getText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/val_CheckRef"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
409. comment("Posted Payment CheckRef Number " + CheckRef)
413. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/btn_Post"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
417. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_BatchJobs/fld_GoTo_Quickjump"), 0, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
421. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_BatchJobs/fld_GoTo_Quickjump"), "runBatchProcess PostBatchPayment_sp", CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
425. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_BatchJobs/fld_GoTo_Quickjump"), Keys.chord(ENTER), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
429. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/lbl_DesktopOption"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
433. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/opt_SuspensepPayment"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
437. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/opt_SuspensepPayment"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
441. driver = getWebDriver()
445. Table = driver.findElement(By.xpath("//div[@id='DesktopSuspensePayments-DesktopSuspensePaymentsScreen-DesktopSuspensePaymentsLV']//tbody"))
449. elementsinColumn = gw.Table.getTableElementsByColumn(Table, 9)
453. comment("Elements after function call to getTableElementsByColumn " + elementsinColumn)
457. if (elementsinColumn.contains(BatchNumber))
1. markPassed("Suspense Payment Batch Number Found")
461. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/opt_AccountSearch"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
465. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/fld_SearchAccount"), SplitAccount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
469. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/icon_SearchAccount"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
473. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/icon_PaymentsDownArrow"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
477. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/opt_PaymentsAccount"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
481. Table1 = driver.findElement(By.xpath("//*[@id='AccountPayments-AccountDetailPaymentsScreen-DirectBillPaymentsListDetail-AccountDBPaymentsLV']//tbody"))
485. elementsinColumn1 = gw.Table.getTableElementsByColumn(Table1, 8)
489. comment("Elements after function call to getTableElementsByColumn " + elementsinColumn1)
493. if (elementsinColumn1.contains(BatchNumber))
1. markPassed("Account Payment Batch Number Found")
497. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/opt_ProducerSearch"))
501. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/fld_SearchProducer"), SplitAgency)
505. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/icon_SearchProducer"))
509. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/icon_AgencyBillPaymentsArrow"))
513. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/opt_PaymentsProducer"))
517. Table2 = driver.findElement(By.xpath("//*[@id='AgencyBillExecutedPayments-PaymentsLV']//tbody"))
521. elementsinColumn2 = gw.Table.getTableElementsByColumn(Table2, 9)
525. comment("Elements after function call to getTableElementsByColumn " + elementsinColumn2)
529. if (elementsinColumn2.contains(BatchNumber))
1. markPassed("Agency Statement Payment Batch Number Found")
533. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/opt_ProducerSearch"))
537. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/fld_SearchProducer"), SplitAgency)
541. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/icon_SearchProducer"))
545. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/opt_TransactionsProducer"))
549. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/Tab_PaymentsProducer"))
553. Table3 = driver.findElement(By.xpath("//*[@id='ProducerTransactions-ProducerTransactionsScreen-PaymentsLV']//tbody"))
557. elementsinColumn3 = gw.Table.getTableElementsByColumn(Table3, 7)
561. comment("Elements after function call to getTableElementsByColumn " + elementsinColumn3)
565. if (elementsinColumn3.contains(CheckRef))
1. markPassed("Agency DB Commission Payment CheckRef Found")
569. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/lbl_DesktopOption"))
573. callTestCase(findTestCase("BillingCenter/BatchPaymentEntry/BC_NavigateBatchPaymentEntryScreen"), [:])
1. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/pge_Navigation/opt_Desktop_Actions"))
5. mouseOver(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/pge_Navigation/act_NewPayment"))
9. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/pge_Navigation/opt_newPayment _BatchPaymentEntry"))
577. for (def index : (0..0))
1. tc_end_Time = System.currentTimeMillis()
5. date_tc_end_Time = dateformat.format(tc_end_Time)
9. (tempRowNum++)
13. testCaseID = testCaseContext.getTestCaseId()
17. testCase = findTestCase(testCaseID)
21. testCaseName = testCase.getName()
25. switch (testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
2. (passedCnt++)
6. break
29. if (testCaseName == "GenerateAndSendReport")
33. if (testCaseName == "GenerateAndSaveReport")
37. if (testCaseName == "GenerateTimeReport")
41. if (!(testCaseName.contains("Submission")) && !(testCaseName.contains("Issurance")) && !(testCaseName.contains("NewAccount")) && !(testCaseName.contains("FNOL")) && !(testCaseName.contains("QuickClaim")) && !(testCaseName.contains("verify")))
1. if (Env_TestSuiteName == "EmailReport")
5. if (Env_TestSuiteName == "GenerateReport")
9. if (Env_TestSuiteName == "GenerateElapsedTimeReport")
13. ts_end_Time = System.currentTimeMillis()
17. date_ts_end_Time = dateformat.format(ts_end_Time)
21. Excel.WirteToExcel(reportSumPath, reportSheet, 1, "Elapsed Time", FormatTime.formatElapsed(ts_end_Time - ts_start_Time))