1. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/lst_Source"), Source, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
5. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_BatchAmount"), BatchAmount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
9. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_BatchAmount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
13. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/lst_Type"), Type, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
17. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_AgencyCode"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
21. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_AgencyCode"), AgencyCode)
25. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_AgencyCode"), Keys.chord(TAB))
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/chk_DBCommissions"))
33. check(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/chk_DBCommissions"))
37. verifyElementChecked(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/chk_DBCommissions"), 0)
41. clearText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Amount"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
45. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Amount"), Amount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
49. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Amount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
53. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_CheckRef"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
57. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_CheckRef"), CheckRef, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
61. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Description"), Description, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
65. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/lst_PaymentInstrument"), PaymentInstrument, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
69. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/btn_Next"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
73. CheckRef = getText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/val_CheckRef"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
77. comment("Posted Payment CheckRef Number " + CheckRef)
81. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/btn_Post"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
85. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_BatchJobs/fld_GoTo_Quickjump"), 0)
89. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_BatchJobs/fld_GoTo_Quickjump"), "runBatchProcess PostBatchPayment_sp")
93. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_BatchJobs/fld_GoTo_Quickjump"), Keys.chord(ENTER))
97. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/opt_ProducerSearch"))
101. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/fld_SearchProducer"), AgencyCode)
105. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/icon_SearchProducer"))
109. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/opt_TransactionsProducer"))
113. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/Tab_PaymentsProducer"))
117. driver = getWebDriver()
121. Table = driver.findElement(By.xpath("//*[@id='ProducerTransactions-ProducerTransactionsScreen-PaymentsLV']//tbody"))
125. elementsinColumn = gw.Table.getTableElementsByColumn(Table, 7)
129. comment("Elements after function call to getTableElementsByColumn " + elementsinColumn)
133. if (elementsinColumn.contains(CheckRef))
1. markPassed("Agency DB Commission Payment CheckRef Found")
137. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/lbl_DesktopOption"))
141. callTestCase(findTestCase("BillingCenter/BatchPaymentEntry/BC_NavigateBatchPaymentEntryScreen"), [:])
1. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/pge_Navigation/opt_Desktop_Actions"))
5. mouseOver(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/pge_Navigation/act_NewPayment"))
9. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/pge_Navigation/opt_newPayment _BatchPaymentEntry"))
145. for (def index : (0..0))
1. tc_end_Time = System.currentTimeMillis()
5. date_tc_end_Time = dateformat.format(tc_end_Time)
9. (tempRowNum++)
13. testCaseID = testCaseContext.getTestCaseId()
17. testCase = findTestCase(testCaseID)
21. testCaseName = testCase.getName()
25. switch (testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
2. (passedCnt++)
6. break
29. if (testCaseName == "GenerateAndSendReport")
33. if (testCaseName == "GenerateAndSaveReport")
37. if (testCaseName == "GenerateTimeReport")
41. if (!(testCaseName.contains("Submission")) && !(testCaseName.contains("Issurance")) && !(testCaseName.contains("NewAccount")) && !(testCaseName.contains("FNOL")) && !(testCaseName.contains("QuickClaim")) && !(testCaseName.contains("verify")))
1. if (Env_TestCaseId == testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
2. iteration = 1
5. Env_Iteration = iteration
9. Env_TestCaseId = testCaseContext.getTestCaseId()
13. Env_TestCaseVariables = testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables()
17. tc_start_Time = System.currentTimeMillis()
21. date_tc_start_Time = dateformat.format(tc_start_Time)