1. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/lst_Source"), Source, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
5. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_BatchAmount"), BatchAmount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
9. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_BatchAmount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
13. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/chk_Split"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
17. check(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/screen_SplitPaymentEntry/chk_Split"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
21. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/lst_Type"), Type, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
25. clearText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Amount"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
29. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Amount"), Amount, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
33. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Amount"), Keys.chord(TAB))
37. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_CheckRef"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
41. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_CheckRef"), CheckRef, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
45. setText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/txt_Description"), Description, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
49. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/lst_PaymentInstrument"), PaymentInstrument, false, CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
53. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/btn_Next"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
57. BatchNumber = getText(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/val_BatchNumber"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
61. comment("Posted Payment Batch Number " + BatchNumber)
65. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/btn_Post"), CONTINUE_ON_FAILURE)
69. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_BatchJobs/fld_GoTo_Quickjump"), 0)
73. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_BatchJobs/fld_GoTo_Quickjump"), "runBatchProcess PostBatchPayment_sp")
77. sendKeys(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_BatchJobs/fld_GoTo_Quickjump"), Keys.chord(ENTER))
81. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/lbl_DesktopOption"))
85. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/opt_SuspensepPayment"))
89. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_MultiplePaymentWizard/opt_SuspensepPayment"))
93. driver = getWebDriver()
97. Table = driver.findElement(By.xpath("//div[@id='DesktopSuspensePayments-DesktopSuspensePaymentsScreen-DesktopSuspensePaymentsLV']//tbody"))
101. elementsinColumn = gw.Table.getTableElementsByColumn(Table, 9)
105. comment("Elements after function call to getTableElementsByColumn " + elementsinColumn)
109. if (elementsinColumn.contains(BatchNumber))
1. markPassed("Suspense Payment Batch Number Found")
113. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/screen_Verify_PostedPayments/lbl_DesktopOption"))
117. callTestCase(findTestCase("BillingCenter/BatchPaymentEntry/BC_NavigateBatchPaymentEntryScreen"), [:])
1. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/pge_Navigation/opt_Desktop_Actions"))
5. mouseOver(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/pge_Navigation/act_NewPayment"))
9. click(findTestObject("BillingCenter/pge_BatchPaymentEntry/pge_Navigation/opt_newPayment _BatchPaymentEntry"))
121. for (def index : (0..0))
1. tc_end_Time = System.currentTimeMillis()
5. date_tc_end_Time = dateformat.format(tc_end_Time)
9. (tempRowNum++)
13. testCaseID = testCaseContext.getTestCaseId()
17. testCase = findTestCase(testCaseID)
21. testCaseName = testCase.getName()
25. switch (testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())
2. (passedCnt++)
6. break
29. if (testCaseName == "GenerateAndSendReport")
33. if (testCaseName == "GenerateAndSaveReport")
37. if (testCaseName == "GenerateTimeReport")
41. if (!(testCaseName.contains("Submission")) && !(testCaseName.contains("Issurance")) && !(testCaseName.contains("NewAccount")) && !(testCaseName.contains("FNOL")) && !(testCaseName.contains("QuickClaim")) && !(testCaseName.contains("verify")))
1. if (Env_TestCaseId == testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
2. iteration = 1
5. Env_Iteration = iteration
9. Env_TestCaseId = testCaseContext.getTestCaseId()
13. Env_TestCaseVariables = testCaseContext.getTestCaseVariables()
17. tc_start_Time = System.currentTimeMillis()
21. date_tc_start_Time = dateformat.format(tc_start_Time)